http://paperweight.com/privacy-policy

Fine Glass Paperweights    410 S. Michigan Ave., Suite #207, Chicago, IL 60605    1-800-538-0766    312-583-1177
Artists
All ArtistsAntique AmericanMelissa AyotteRick AyotteAntique BaccaratModern BaccaratBob BanfordRay BanfordAntique ClichyJim D'OnofrioJohn DeaconsDrew EbelhareTwists Glass StudioDavid GraeberRandall GrubbEric HansenCharles Kaziun Junior Lundberg StudiosDamon MacNaught Orient & Flume Parabelle Glass Perthshire PaperweightsCathy RichardsonColin RichardsonKen RosenfeldAlison RuzsaAntique Saint LouisModern Saint LouisClinton SmithGordon SmithPaul StankardDebbie TarsitanoVictor TrabuccoMayauel WardPaul YsartAll Artists
New
Search
Advanced Search
My Collections
Auctions
Current Auction
Current Auction Catalog
Sell My Paperweights
Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.theglassgallery.com and L.H. Selman, LTD dba The Glass Gallery and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to L.H. Selman, LTD dba The Glass Gallery include www.theglassgallery.com and The Glass Gallery. The The Glass Gallery website is an E-Commerce site and information hub for fine glass paperweights and glass art. By using the The Glass Gallery website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information The Glass Gallery may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase The Glass Gallery's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by The Glass Gallery. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the The Glass Gallery website.
The Glass Gallery encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from The Glass Gallery so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. The Glass Gallery is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the The Glass Gallery website.
Use of your Personal Information The Glass Gallery collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
The Glass Gallery may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from The Glass Gallery and its affiliates. The Glass Gallery may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
The Glass Gallery does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
The Glass Gallery may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to The Glass Gallery, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
The Glass Gallery will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on The Glass Gallery or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of The Glass Gallery; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of The Glass Gallery, or the public.
Use of Cookies The The Glass Gallery website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize The Glass Gallery pages, or register with The Glass Gallery site or services, a cookie helps The Glass Gallery to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same The Glass Gallery website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the The Glass Gallery features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the The Glass Gallery services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, The Glass Gallery uses the following:
GeoTrust
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
Children Under Thirteen The Glass Gallery does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from The Glass Gallery by contacting us here: - Email:
- Phone: 312-583-1177
Changes to this Statement The Glass Gallery will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. The Glass Gallery encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how The Glass Gallery is protecting your information.
Contact Information The Glass Gallery welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that The Glass Gallery has not adhered to this Statement, please contact The Glass Gallery at:
L.H. Selman, LTD dba The Glass Gallery 410 S. Michigan Ave, Suite 207 Chicago, Illinois 60605
Email Address:
Welcome.
410 S. Michigan Ave., Suite #207, Chicago, IL 60605 1-800-538-0766 | 312-583-1177 |
Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy
